{
    "id": "9cff2b23dd264c7a82478c21d4e8b472",
    "title": "Articles Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "She has been living in ................................. Bangkok for three years.",
            "description": "Articles are not normally used before the names of countries, cities or continents.",
            "answers": [
                "a",
                "the",
                "No article"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "......................... Nile is the longest river in the world.",
            "description": "Articles are used before the names of rivers.",
            "answers": [
                "A",
                "The",
                "No Article"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Some of my friends live in ............................... United States of America.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "the",
                "No article"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "............................. Netherlands is also called ............................ Holland.",
            "description": "The article the is used with United States, United Kingdom, Netherlands and United Arab Emirates.",
            "answers": [
                "The, no article",
                "No articles are required",
                "The, the"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He spent his holidays in .............................. Alps.",
            "description": "Articles are used before the names of mountain ranges.",
            "answers": [
                "a",
                "the",
                "No article"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "............................. Andes is the longest mountain range in the world.",
            "description": "Articles are used before the names of mountain ranges.",
            "answers": [
                "A",
                "The",
                "No article"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "............................ Mount Everest is the highest mountain in the world.",
            "description": "Articles are not used before the names of individual mountains.",
            "answers": [
                "A",
                "The",
                "No article"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "............................. Bahamas is a group of islands in ............................ West Atlantic Ocean.",
            "description": "Articles are used before the names of groups of islands and oceans.",
            "answers": [
                "No articles are required",
                "The, the",
                "The, a"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": ".............................. Sahara is the largest desert in the world.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "The",
                "A",
                "No article"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "............................. India is a country in ..................................",
            "description": "Articles are not normally used before the names of countries, cities or continents.",
            "answers": [
                "The, the",
                "The, a",
                "No articles are required"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "She emigrated to .............................. Canada in",
            "description": "Articles are not normally used before the names of countries or cities.",
            "answers": [
                "a",
                "the",
                "No article"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "They spent their holidays on ……………………… island.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "a",
                "an",
                "No article"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}